watchers.news 2017-11-19

# The Watchers - Daily news service | Watchers.NEWS

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.

  * We collect information you provide us (nickname and email) and your user agent when you submit forms or make comments.
  * Your email will also be collected when you subscribe to our newsletter. We use Google Feedburner for newsletter service.
  * We will never ask you for credit card information and we urge you not to write any such information on the forms of the website.
  * We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future
  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter or submit your personal information on forms.
  * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

This website uses Google Analytics. Please refer to the following policies on Google's website for detailed information:

These are the outlines on the types of personal information received and collected by us and how it is used.

#### Log files

Like many other Web sites, Watchers.NEWS makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and web beacons

We do use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

#### DoubleClick DART cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on thewatchers.adorraeli.com.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to thewatchers.adorraeli.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

_This policy was last modified on March 29, 2017._

* * *
